<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!--
English language XML file, used for page contents.

Developed by AvB, aliases Uther, UPendragon.
Date   : 07-2023
Version: 1.0

(c) 2023, artvabas
-->
<root>
	
	<!--Default.aspx-->

	<default_data>
		<header>Software Solutions</header><!--node 0-->
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<paragraph><!--node 1-->
			If you're looking for custom made software, but don't want the worries about how to develop, maintain, hosting and networking.
			Then don't look any further, because artvabas can handle a goat, and the one who can handle a goat, can handle everything.
		</paragraph>
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<paragraph><!--node 2-->
			artvabas is specialized in developing software solution for non-profit organizations and individuals.
			Not only for developing the software but also for software maintenances, hosting and software networking.
		</paragraph>
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<paragraph><!--node 3-->
			But the main thing is, you'll be always in control. You decide what and how you want it, and how far our service can go for you.
			All this for a good price, sometimes for only the expenses or even for free. Yeah we're fun-crazy but very professional, open
			and transparent. And why? Didn't I tell you about the goat!
		</paragraph>
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<button_link>Read more</button_link><!--node 4-->
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<header>Getting started</header><!--node 5-->
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<paragraph><!--node 6-->
			How it works? Just fill in the contact form or send us an email with your wishes. We'll make contact with you for a short interview to see
			if we understand all your desires. Then...
		</paragraph>
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<link>Read more</link><!--node 7-->
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<header>Aftercare</header><!--node 8-->
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<paragraph><!--node 9-->
			When your application is up and running, the first two years you can enjoy our guarantee program. After this, you can decide
			to get advantage of one of artvabas maintenance...
		</paragraph>
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<link>Read more</link><!--node 10-->
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<header>Donation</header><!--node 11-->
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<paragraph><!--node 12-->
			If you are a non-profit organization or an individual the cost can be free or as low as it can be, depends on the application artvabas have to develop for you.
			In matter of fact, we use a donation system for...
		</paragraph>
	</default_data>
	<default_data>
		<link>Read more</link><!--node 13-->
	</default_data>
	
	<!--About.aspx-->

	<about_data>
		<title>About</title><!--node 0-->
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<paragraph><!--node 1-->
			artvabas isn't a company, organization or a institution. artvabas is a individual who has worked as ICT Manager and as Software Engineer
			for the last 30 years. artvabas love to build software and solving ICT related issues.
		</paragraph>
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<header>Goal</header><!--node 2-->
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<paragraph><!--node 3-->
			artvabas goal is to help non-profit organizations and individuals with their software and ICT related ideas or issues. This on a semi
			non-profit basis, the only thing artvabas is asking is a small donation for your appreciation. If there are needs of any kind of
			Internet related services, such as hosting databases or cloud related networks etc. those cost are fully billed to you, without any profit
			from our side (see also
		</paragraph>
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<link_donation>Donation</link_donation><!--node 4-->
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<header>Why?</header><!--node 5-->
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<paragraph>	<!--node 6-->
			Because lots of non-profit organizations, such as; sport clubs, public organization, public movement, foundation of public utility, public institution,
			various foundations etc. often cope with poor quality of software or ICT related structures. The main reason for this is often money or the knowledge.
			They often don't have the ability to hire professionals for developing the software they need or for other ICT related solutions. And it is always
			good to give something back to the society, thats why artvabas is volunteering.
		</paragraph>
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<header>What kind</header><!--node 7-->
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<paragraph><!--node 8-->
			artvabas can develop and maintain all kinds of; mobile (phone, tablet), desktop and web applications. But also databases, IoT (Internet of Things) and
			cloud solutions.
		</paragraph>
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<see_also_title>See also...</see_also_title><!--node 9-->
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<see_also_button>Get started</see_also_button><!--node 10-->
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<see_also_button>Aftercare</see_also_button><!--node 11-->
	</about_data>
	<about_data>
		<see_also_button>Donation</see_also_button><!--node 12-->
	</about_data>
	
	<!--Contact.aspx-->
	
	<contact_data>
		<title>Contact</title><!--node 0-->
	</contact_data>
	<contact_data>
		<subtitle>How to contact.</subtitle><!--node 1-->
	</contact_data>
	<contact_data><!--node 2-->
		<paragraph>
			If you have any question or you want artvabas to build you an application, then please fill in the contact form
			underneath and click on send.
		</paragraph>
	</contact_data>
	<contact_data>
		<see_also_title>See also...</see_also_title><!--node 3-->
	</contact_data>
	<contact_data>
		<see_also_button>Get started</see_also_button><!--node 4-->
	</contact_data>
	<contact_data>
		<see_also_button>Aftercare</see_also_button><!--node 5-->
	</contact_data>
	<contact_data>
		<see_also_button>Donation</see_also_button><!--node 6-->
	</contact_data>

	<!-- ContactControl.ascx -->

	<contact-control-data>
		<about>You want to contact artvabas about?:</about><!--node 0-->
	</contact-control-data>
	<contact-control-data>
		<kindof>What kind of application(s)?:</kindof><!--node 1-->
	</contact-control-data>
	<contact-control-data>
		<platform>For which platform(s)?:</platform><!--node 2-->
	</contact-control-data>
	<contact-control-data>
		<email>What's your contact email address?:</email><!--node 3-->
	</contact-control-data>
	<contact-control-data>
		<phone>What's your contact phone number?:</phone><!--node 4-->
	</contact-control-data>
	<contact-control-data>
		<letter>Your letter?:</letter><!--node 5-->
	</contact-control-data>
	<contact-control-data>
		<submit>Send</submit><!-- node 6-->
	</contact-control-data>

</root>

